ISIS Lombard, Infi, Tata LC, NLC India,
Carnitaka Bank, Kodak Bank. Stocks in
news January 14th quarterly results
today. companies including Infosys, HDFC
AMC, ISIS Credential AMC, Union Bank of
India, Billion Brains Garage Ventures
Grow, Anandrai Share and Stock Brokers,
Audit, Yaba Burla Money, Den Networks,
HDB Financial Services, Indian Overseas
Bank, Mangalore Refinery and
Prochemicals and other will announce
their results for December 2025 quarter
today.
Corporate actions today. Shares of Kodak
Mahindra Bank and Ammer realy and
infraindia shall trade X date for stock
split today. Isisai Lombard general
insurance company. The general insurance
player reported a 9% yoy fall in the net
profit at 658.8
rupees cr while total income grew 12.4%
yoi to 6,610.2
2 rupees cr. In the December 2025
quarter, net premium earned rose 12.7%
yoy to 5,685.3
rupees crer while operating profit
dropped 16.7% yi to 571.1
rupees crer. Tata LC the IT solutions
player reported a 45.3%
yoy fall in the net profit at 108.9 crer
while revenue increased 1.5% yoi to
953.5
rupees cr for the quarter ended on
December 31st 2025
its expectational loss stood at 95.7
rupees cr for the reported quarter
citing a one-time increase in employee
fee benefit provisions following India's
new labor codes.
NLC India the state-run power firm has
signed a memorandum of understanding Mao
with the Gujarat government for the
development of large-scale renewable
energy projects in the state. These
include solar, wind, hybrid and battery
energy storage projects with an
investment potential of 25,000 rupees
crer. Carnitaka bank. The private lender
has enabled a facility for the payment
of carnitaka government skina 2-year
receipts through its internet banking
platform providing a secure realtime and
paperless receipt system. Interarchch
Building Solutions, the pre-engineered
building products player, has received
an order worth 130 rupees cr for the
manufacturing of a pre-engineered steel
building system.
Just dial the internet-based services
provider reported a 10.2% yoy fall to
117.9
rupees crer while revenue increased 6.4%
4% yoy to 305.7
rupees cr for the October December 2025
quarter. EBITDA increased 9.6% y to 95.2
rupees cr in Q3 while EBITDA margin
improved to 31.1%
yoi for the reported quarter. Thomas
Cook India the travel services and
solutions provider player has signed a
memorandum of understanding Mao with the
Gujarat government to boost and promote
Gujarat s domestic tourism.
Five, Pyaw Capital, the financial
services provider's net profit declined
24enter yoy to 12.3 rupees crer while
revenue dropped 7enter yoy to 79.3
rupees cr for the quarter ended on
December 31st 2025.
Responsive Industries Babnit Singh Chada
has resigned as the chief financial
officer CFO of the company effective
January 12th due to personal reasons.
The company is in the process of
appointing a suitable candidate for the
position of CFO and key managerial
personnel. KMP
OMAX the real estate developer announced
Rs 500 crore investment to develop Omax
Chow Ludana a mixeduse high street
retail and luxury residential project
aimed at strengthening organized retail
and urban infrastructure in Punjab s
largest industrial city. Disclaimer.
This article provides stock market news
forformational purposes only and should
not be construed as investment advice.
Readers are encouraged to consult with a
qualified financial adviser before
making any investment decisions.